A Guide to the Office of the Dean of Students Office Administrative Files, 1950-2000
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series VI: Associate Dean of Students,Annette Gibbs/Ronald Stump
  - Orientation Evaluation Plans--S. Powers 1992 (Box 40)
  - Graduate/Professional Students Orientation Activities 1992 (Box 40)
  - Orientation Correspondence 1992 (Box 40)
  - Graduate/Professional Student Orientation 1992 (Box 40)
  - Orientation--Composite Schedule 1992 (Box 40)
  - Orientation Brochure 1992 (Box 40)
  - Orientation 1991 (Box 40)
  - Orientation Correspondence 1992 (Box 40)
  - Opening Move-in 1991 (Box 40)
  - New Student Mailings 1992 (Box 40)
  - Orientation Planning 1992 (Box 40)
  - Orientation Brochures 1992 (Box 40)
  - Pep Band Charges 1993 (Box 40)
  - Presentations on CIOs to the Board 1987 (Box 40)
  - CIO Implementation Presentation 1988 (Box 40)
  - Presentation on Orientation 1990 (Box 40)
  - University Judiciary Committee Presentation 1993 (Box 40)
  - President's Retreat 1987 (Box 40)
  - President's Retreat 1987 (Box 41)
  - President's Retreat Evaluation Report 1987 (Box 41)
  - Review of Orientation Goals and Activities 1988 (Box 41)
  - Student Self-Governance Meeting 1987 (Box 41)
  - Student Activities Space Assessment 1991 (Box 41)
  - Space Management Task Force--Ron Stump 1987 (Box 41)
  - Space Allocation 1990 (Box 41)
  - Student Activities Building 1981 (Box 41)
  - Student Activities Building Usage 1987 (Box 41)
  - Task Force On Space Management 1987 (Box 41)
  - Psychological Panels 1987 (Box 41)
  - Racism 101 1992 (Box 41)
  - Rallies and Sit-ins 1990 (Box 41)
  - Rallies 1987 (Box 41)
  - Residence Life Policy 1982-1991 (Box 41)
  - CIO Fall Registration Fundraising 1991 (Box 41)
  - Fall Registration Request Form 1992 (Box 41)
  - Activities on the Rotunda Portico 1992 (Box 41)
  - The Restoration Ball Committee 1991 (Box 41)
  - Roundtable of Black Greek Affairs Undergrad/Grad Chapters 1987 (Box 41)
  - Safety on Grounds 1992 (Box 41)
  - Guidelines for Student Activities Funds Allocation 1973 (Box 41)
  - Student Activities Committee 1989-1990 (Box 42)
  - Student Activities Committee Budget and Allocations 1984-1985 (Box 42)
  - SAC Correspondence and Appeals 1985-1986 (Box 42)
  - SAC Correspondence and Appeals 1984-1985 (Box 42)
  - Student Activities Committee Budget and Allocations 1985-1986 (Box 42)
  - SAC Budget 1987 (Box 42)
  - SAF Allocations 1985-1986 (Box 42)
  - Student Activities Committee Budget and Allocations 1986-1987 (Box 42)
  - Budgets for Appropriations 1988 (Box 43)
  - Sale of Goods by Student Organizations 1974 (Box 43)
  - SAF Funds for Newcomb Hall Expansion 1993 (Box 43)
  - Student Organization Survey 1989 (Box 43)
  - Liens on Equipment purchased by SAF 1986 (Box 43)
  - SAC (Student Activities Committee) 1987-1988 (Box 43)
  - Appropriations Committee 1989 (Box 43)
  - SAC (Student Appropriations Committee) 1988-1989 (Box 43)
  - Student Activities Business Manager: Annual Report to the Student Activities Committee 1984-1985 (Box 43)
  - Student Activities Business Manager: Annual Report to the Student Activities Committee 1986-1987 (Box 44)
  - Student Activities Business Manager: Annual Report to the Student Activities Committee 1990-1991 (Box 44)
  - Scheduling Committee 1987 (Box 44)
  - SCHEV Report 1992-1993 (Box 44)
  - Directory of UVA Selected Scholarships and Fellowships 1987 (Box 44)
  - Student Assessment 1989 (Box 44)
  - Student Organization Fundraising 1988-1989 (Box 44)
  - Student Organization Fundraising Projects Policy 1989 (Box 44)
  - Sexual Assault Mediation 1991 (Box 44)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia Campus Assault 1992 (Box 44)
  - SLS Landlord/Tenant Agreement 1988 (Box 44)
  - Student Activities Business Manager's Audit 1986 (Box 44)
  - Student Activities Committee 1994 (Box 44)
  - Student Council 1981-1982 (Box 44)
  - Tolerance on Campus Proposal 1992 (Box 44)
  - Student Legal Services Description Statement 1989 (Box 44)
  - United Ministry 1987-1988 (Box 44)
  - University Family Housing Association 1950-1979 (Box 44)
  - UU - University Hall 1984 (Box 44)
  - Changes for the use of University Hall 1986 (Box 44)
  - University of Virginia Chapel 1980 (Box 44)
  - The University Report 1986-1987 (Box 44)
  - University-wide Deans of Student Affairs 1988 (Box 45)
  - UU--Publicity Committee 1983 (Box 45)
  - Purchasing Procedure for items for resale 1988 (Box 45)
  - UU Resources Committee 1983-1989 (Box 45)
  - University Union Retreat 1993 (Box 45)
  - Secretaries' Workload 1986 (Box 45)
  - UU Short Courses Committee 1983-1992 (Box 45)
  - UU--Student Development Programming Matrix 1990 (Box 45)
  - Study of University Union 1980 (Box 45)
  - Subcommittee on Black Student Programming/ VPCUU SAB 1988 (Box 45)
  - University Union--Summer (3 folders) 1984-1988 (Box 45)
  - University Union Proposed Activities Fee 1985 (Box 45)
  - University Union--Summer Programming 1991 (Box 45)
  - Summer Union (3 folders) 1990-1992 (Box 45)
  - University Union--Surf Charlottesville 1988 (Box 45)
  - Ticketron Service 1987 (Box 45)
  - University Union--Training Camp 1986 (Box 45)
  - University Union--Travel Committee 1983-1987 (Box 45)
  - University Union--Visionaries Committee 1986 (Box 46)
  - University Union--Wellness/Committee Center 1988 (Box 46)
  - University Union--Xerox Machine 1985 (Box 46)
  - Vice-chair Workshop (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 46)
  - Committee on University Union and the Student Activities Building (9 folders) 1985-1994 (Box 46)
  - VPCUUSAB Sub Committee on Space Usage 1986 (Box 46)
  - Vice President's Committee on SAB/UU 1987-1988 (Box 46)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs 1981 (Box 46)
  - University Union--Ushers' Committee 1983-1989 (Box 47)
  - VCPUU Visionary Sub Committee 1986 (Box 47)
  - Weekend Programming UU 1989 (Box 47)
  - Upperclass Community Council 1992 (Box 47)
  - Venable/Emmet Street Neighborhood Study 1988-1989 (Box 47)
  - Videos in Residence Hall Areas 1993 (Box 47)
  - Virginia Film Festival 1992 (Box 47)
  - Aruna Viswadoss 1993 (Box 47)
  - Virginia Festival of American Film 1985 (Box 47)
  - VCCS Student Leaders Conference 1993 (Box 47)
  - Virginians for Justice 1989 (Box 47)
  - West Main Street Corridor Study 1993 (Box 47)
  - Women and Higher Education 1993 (Box 47)
  - Women at UVA 1992 (Box 47)
  - Women's Leadership Development Program 1992 (Box 47)
  - Working Group on Orientation and Personal Briefings 1992 (Box 47)
- Series VII: Restricted Files (Box 48)